http://www.stlcc.edu/college-policy-procedures/consumer-information/privacy-policy.aspx

Privacy Policy
College Policies and ProceduresCollege Policies and ProceduresCollege Policies and ProceduresAcademic Rights and ResponsibilitiesAccess Services Student HandbookAccommodations StatementAccreditationCampus Crime ReportsCampus Guidelines on Distribution of InformationClosing Procedures & NotificationsComputer Use and File SharingConsumer InformationLegal DisclaimerPrivacy PolicyLactation/Breastfeeding InformationGDPR FAQCopyright InformationDrug and Alcohol Abuse PreventionEnrollment ReportsFacilities and Services for Students with DisabilitiesGuide to ReligionsPrivacy of Student Records (FERPA)Refund Policy and Requirements for Withdrawal and Return of Federal Financial AidRegistration & Medical AppealsSTLCC CaresStudent Conduct Rights and ResponsibilitiesTitle IX
Privacy Policy
St. Louis Community College is committed to protecting your privacy.
Any information you voluntarily provide to us through a St. Louis Community College
website, such as an email address, name or phone number, will never be sold or traded
to other colleges, universities, non-profit organizations or businesses.
Information Gathered Automatically
Unless you take steps to browse the Internet anonymously, or opt-out, St. Louis Community College, like most institutions and organizations on the Internet,
tracks web browsing patterns to inform understanding of how our sites are being used.
Generic information is collected through the use of “cookies,” which are text files
placed on your computer, to evaluate usage patterns so that we can improve both content
and distribution. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings
on your browser; however, doing so may prevent you from using the full functionality
of all of our websites. The generic information we collect is based on an IP address,
which is the location of a computer or network, and is not linked to your specific
email address in any of the reports or other material compiled by St. Louis Community
College. St. Louis Community College will not associate your IP address and web usage
data with any other information held by St. Louis Community College that can specifically
identify you unless required to do so by law.
Some sections of St. Louis Community College-owned websites use Google Analytics,
a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies to
help us analyze how users use our sites. The information generated by the cookie about
your use of the website includes your IP address. This information will be transmitted
to and stored by Google on its servers. Google will use this information for the purpose
of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity, and
providing other services relating to Internet usage. Google may also transfer this
information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties
process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address
with any other data held by Google. By using this website, you consent to the processing
of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
Please visit the following pages for more information on Google Analytics terms of use and Google’s privacy practices.
Information You Provide to Us
To communicate effectively with visitors to our websites, we may ask you for personally-identifiable
information that can include, by way of illustration, name, email address or phone
number. St. Louis Community College will never sell or trade personally-identifiable
information you voluntarily provide to us such as name, email address or phone number,
to other colleges, universities, nonprofit organizations or businesses unless one
or more of the following conditions apply:
We have your consent to share the information.
We are sharing such information in response to subpoenas, court orders or legal processes.
In certain instances, in order to provide information and services, or as required
by law, St. Louis Community College may disseminate non-personally and personally-identifiable
information you provide us to third parties and officials/departments within the College.
In these instances, the information provided to the third party or College entity
shall be limited to the extent necessary to provide the user-requested information
and/or services, or as required by applicable law enforcement agencies.
External Links
Some St. Louis Community College websites may contain links to external websites not
owned by, or officially affiliated with, St. Louis Community College in any way. St.
Louis Community College is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content
of such websites.
Your Personal Account
Any user that chooses to use St. Louis Community College’s websites is responsible
for maintaining the confidentiality of his or her account and password, if any, and
for restricting access to his or her computer, and agrees to accept responsibility
for all activities that occur under his or her account or password. The user agrees
that any billing and registration information provided on the websites will be accurate
and complete.
Security
St. Louis Community College implements security measures to promote the confidentiality,
integrity, and availability of any information in its possession (or control). We
utilize Transport Layer Security (TLS) encryption technology for instances where the
College’s websites request or provide personal information of the user. The TLS technology’s
purpose is to protect users’ information from being viewed by an outside third party.
Some features on this website may enable credit card transactions in order for users
to purchase a variety of goods and services.  Credit card transactions are completely
voluntary. Additionally, the College subcontracts the processing on online transactions
to PCI DSS certified vendors to further promote effective security.
While the security of users’ personal information is of the utmost importance to St.
Louis Community College, we cannot guarantee the security of any information the user
chooses to disclose online. Any information the user chooses to disclose to St. Louis
Community College is done at his/her own risk.
Changes to This Policy
When we make changes to this policy, the changes will be highlighted on the top of
this page for one month before going into effect. The highlights will then remain
on top of the page for three months to keep you informed of the change.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this website,
you may contact: St. Louis Community College Marketing and Communications Department Telephone: 314.644.9264Email: stlccpim@stlcc.edu
Privacy of Student Records (FERPA)
The Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) affords eligible students certain
rights with respect to their education records. An “eligible student” under FERPA
is a student who is 18 years of age or older or who attends a postsecondary institution.
Last updated: June 29, 2018
©
Back to top
